const week1Data = [
  {
    question: "IoT stands for ____________.",
    options: [
      "Internet of Tasks",
      "Internet of Tuples",
      "Internet of Things",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Internet of Things",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following technologies have unified and has resulted in the evolution of IoT?",
    options: [
      "High-power embedded systems",
      "Super Computing",
      "Engine Technology",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are the enablers of IoT?",
    options: ["RFID", "Nanotechnology", "Sensors", "All of these"],
    answer: "All of these",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a function of an IoT LAN?",
    options: [
      "Long range communication, global",
      "World wide connections",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "Neither (a) Nor (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The integration of existing devices, smart devices, and constrained nodes in a singular framework is one of the reasons for the address crunch in IoT.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Multi-homing, a node/network is connected to a single network for improved reliability.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is/are the approach/approaches for multi-homing?",
    options: [
      "Proxy-based approach",
      "Gateway-based approach",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "IPv6 uses ____________ notation for its representation.",
    options: ["Hexadecimal", "Binary", "Decimal", "None of these"],
    answer: "Hexadecimal",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The parameters sensed by a sensor may be sent to the cloud for further processing.",
    options: ["False", "True"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The IPv6 notation uses ___________________ number of bits to represent an address.",
    options: ["64", "128", "Both (a) and (b)", "Neither (a) nor (b)"],
    answer: "128",
  },
  {
    question: "A sensor is -",
    options: [
      "Only sensitive to the measured property",
      "Insensitive to any other property that what the sensor is made to sense",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "We classify sensors based on -",
    options: ["Output", "Data type", "Both (a) and (b)", "None of these"],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a correct statement?",
    options: [
      "Controlling AC loads using low DC signals",
      "Relays are electromechanical",
      "Relays are actuators",
      "All of these",
    ],
    answer: "All of these",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Based on the output, sensors are classified as ____________________.",
    options: ["Analog", "Digital", "Both (a) and (b)", "Neither (a) nor (b)"],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "Soft actuators are -",
    options: [
      "Polymer-based",
      "Mechanical",
      "Electromechanical",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Polymer-based",
  },
];
